<!-- This is a sample PXML.xml file making use of many different things.-->
<PXML xmlns="http://openpandora.org/namespaces/PXML">
<package id="hase_prototype-hase_prototype-12345">
<version major="1" minor="5" release="4" build="15"/>
<author name="Ziz" website="http://ziz.openhandhelds.org"/>
<titles>
<title lang="en_US">
Hase
</title>
</titles>
<descriptions>
<description lang="en_US">
Hase is a game about hares in space. It is a bit like Worms or Artillery, but with gravitation.
The game itself is licsensed under GPLv2+.
The used fonts are Pixel Mania by HiBan (CC-BY-SA) and DejaVu Sans (Public Domain)

Changelog
=========

1.5.4.15:
- Fixed the ghost arrow bug
- Static linking of hase to remove the need for LD_LIBRARY_PATH
- Added sheep sprite set (thx @ Binky)
- Added skeletal cow err... horse sprite set (thx @ Levi)
- New explosion sound (better and quieter)
- Improved sound of cluster bomb explosion

1.5.4.14:
- Showing the connection status of players while waiting for their turn

1.5.4.13:
- Fixed a bug, which made the heartbeat function run forever
- Fixed ingame chat for devices with onscreen keyboard like GCW

1.5.4.12:
- Fixed a bug for local hotseat playing, which caused the game to crash

1.5.4.11:
- Second local player got kicked in an online game and went Zombie
- Message, if the client becomes a zombie for the other players
- Fixed a bug about resizing the game window

1.5.4.10:
- Bug fix for building stuff on the border (thx @ sheepluva)
- No zig zag in background for waiting for turn data
- Fixed a bug about a flickering screen while entering chat messages
- Removed the "Prototype" in the gcw description
- More space for the game names in the game list in the lobby
- Added warning sound if turn begins
- Redrawing the level border every time
- Added new sprite (thx @ Holysmoke)

1.5.4.9:
- Fixed two crash bugs on resizing
- Added a logo made by comradekingu
- Added possibility to play online / watch replays without being online in the chat
- Fixed the menu size for most cases
- Improved dolphin

1.5.4.8:
- Showing global chat ingame, but greyed out
- Fixed font size for small resolution devices like the GCW
- Removing nubs for pandora (I doubt anybody used it)

1.5.4.7:
- Added fast forward for games for boring AI or replays

1.5.4.6:
- Fixed bug with chat input while chat window not open
- Different button mappings for menu and ingame
- Two new sprites (thx @ Comradekingu)
- Fixed low chance of seg fault right after start of an online game

1.5.4.5:
- Server optimizations for older php versions
- Button mapping while ingame
- Windows only: Removed asking for compressed data
- a new level texture (thx @ Binky)
- a new sprite (thx @ Binky)1.5.4.4:
- Compression of outgoing turn data (again up to 98% data bandwidth saving)
- Button mapping is adjustable

1.5.4.4:
- Compression of outgoing turn data (again up to 98% data bandwidth saving)
- Button mapping is adjustable

1.5.4.3:
- Asking the server to give gzip compressed data. Saved up to 98% of data bandwidth.
- Sound warning at end of turn
- Mine make noises now
- Chat is fading out ingame
- Pandora only: Toggling between fullscreen and windowed mode with the Pandora button
- Inverted button images to be more clear

1.5.4.2:
- Rsotation speed of the cross haire depends on the weapon power
- Targeting line is above cross haire
- Fixed a _very_ rare and uncommon crash because of division by zero
- Set the ingame chat to appear for 1 minute instead of only 20 seconds (testwise)

1.5.4.1:
- Fixed a bug in the HTTP handling code, which made online game unplayable slow

1.5.4:
- Fixed bug on gcw, which made the game unplayable
- (Hopefully) fixed a bug, which made a client crash right after the start if a game with a chance of ~10%
- Automaticly reconnect of IRC loose connection
- Added logging for irc
- Less time between two downloads of a turn to avoid wifi energy saving, which slows down the whole game
- Fixed a crash, when exiting a game via removing the last player
- Creating backups from the OPKs for the GCW, too
- Tomato sprites instead of "Weapon points"
- Line between player and cross haire for easier aiming
- Removed confusing "1 minute timeout" message
- Building tool can build in the ground, but more savety distance to hares
- No sending of empty messages in Chats
- Chat is now [Start] ingame
- Fixed error message if server is not avaible

1.5.3.7:
- Telling when a game happened for replays

1.5.3.6:
- If the game master leaves the game, the game is not deleted from the game list, except (s)he want it.

1.5.3.5:
- Using Menu as fourth button in Linux/Windows

1.5.3.4:
- Line break for ingame chat (Really, you guys talk to much! ;)
- No flickering when entering text while a loading screen is active

1.5.3.3:
- Added spectate modus
- You can even spectate already started, but not yet finished games!

1.5.3.2:
- Recompile with NEON support (forgot it in 1.5.3.1)
- Some little speed optimizations

1.5.3.1:
- Some sparrow3d improvements to draw faster
- Showing the needed server version in the lobby

1.5.3:
- Fixed a bug, that the very close use of the build tool could freeze the game

1.5.2.2:
- Improved handling of disconnects (now called "Zombies" ingame)
- Fixed jump while typing
- No message filter for irc messages in replays

1.5.2.1:
- Right aligned text input if more text than fits in the window
- No movement while typing
- If admin leaves game, the game is not shown in the game list anymore
- rotation stays fix when no gravitation
- Less network spam
- Removed "Aiming 100%" label above AI after it shoot

1.5.2:
- Using NEON for little speed up
- Fixed a bug in the particle system

1.5.1:
- Added mini map

1.5.0.3
- Improved user name checking of IRC nick

1.5.0.2
- Fixed a bug, which fucked the deterministic, which is baaaad
- Replacing spaces with underscore in nicknames

1.5.0.1
- bigger sprites for small screens
- Fixed keyboard-gui-collision
- Backspace button for onscreen keyboard devices (like the GCW)

1.5.0
- More sprites
- Sprites chooseable
- Username saving
- Username guessing with C4A profile information
- server improvements
- better weapon illustration
- Noticement if sprite is used by another player
- Better camera movement
- Username has to be choosen in lobby
- IRC chat
- Chat in lobby
- Sending and receiving chat messages from within the game
- Random button for insult in chat
- Too expensive weapons are greyed out
- Showing level border
- New weapons:
	- A bigger and a smaller building tool
	- Cluster bomb
	- Mine shooter
	- Super jump
	- Weapon point harvesting
	- Little damage shoot without gravity
	- High damage shoot without gravity
	- Instant kill
	- Forced super jump
- Added items:
	- health
	- more weapon points
	- mine
	
1.4.7.2
- Added button arrow images to sparrow3d and use them now in hase in the help

1.4.7.1
- Fixed crash if last player removed in online game (thx @zear)

1.4.7
- Fixed small resolution sprites
- Improved targeting
- Improved button mapping for handhelds without keyboard

1.4.6
- faster showing of own messages in chat
- level color for the bullet traces
- better and new default values for creating a game

1.4.5:
- Added option to not rotate the level, but the bunny
- Added option to invert the controls of the bunny is upside down
- Improved the particle effect (should be faster)

1.4.4:
- Fixed broken network play

1.4.3:
- Arrow stays at minimal size while zooming to see where you are aiming at large zoom-outs
- Circle around active hare to tell which of your characters you are currently controlling
- Options menu for setting like volume, zooming behaviour and hare markation
- Changeable particle size
- Added Sound

1.4.2:
- An option to hide the player names on demand for better aiming when you have a lot of the screen area covered with the names
- Improved colours

1.4.1:
- Fixed little bug after finished turn in online game
- AI is smarter (no friendly fire)
- Faster canceling online game
- Canceled online game will have no replay

1.4:
- 5s extra time after last bullet
- 3 weapon points per turn
- Locking zoom
- Improved Aiming
- New health bar
- Fixed a bug in the bullet calculation
- improved button mapping, using SP_PRACTICE
- Writing down tractory while flying
- New window approach
- Menu
- Multiple hares per player
- New controls
- Global health bar
- Particle Effect
- 6 Weapons


1.3:
- network support
- Start of change logging

</description>
</descriptions>
<icon src="./hase_prototype.png"/>
</package>
<application id="hase_prototype-hase_prototype-12345" appdata="hase_prototype">
<exec command="./hase.sh"/>
<version major="1" minor="5" release="4" build="15" type="release"/>
<!--This program's version-->
<osversion major="1" minor="0" release="0" build="0"/>
<!--The minimum OS version required-->
<author name="Ziz" website="http://ziz.openhandhelds.org"/>
<!--Optional email and website, name required-->
<titles>
<title lang="en_US">
Hase
</title>
</titles>
<title lang="en_US">
Hase
</title>
<!--Extra <title> block for compatibility with OS versions before HF6-->
<descriptions>
<description lang="en_US">
Hase is a worms like game with gravitation. And hares instead of worms.
</description>
</descriptions>
<description lang="en_US">
Hase is a worms like game with gravitation. And hares instead of worms.
</description>
<!--Extra <description> block for compatibility with OS versions before HF6-->
<icon src="./hase_prototype.png"/>
<licenses>
<license name="GPLv2+" url="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html" sourcecodeurl="https://github.com/theZiz/hase"/>
<!--Optional url and sourcecodeurl, mandatory name-->
</licenses>
<previewpics>
<pic src="previews/hase1.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase2.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase3.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase4.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase5.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase6.png"/>
<pic src="previews/hase7.png"/>
</previewpics>
<info name="Hase Readme" type="text" src="hase_readme.txt"/>
<!--the categories has to conform to the FDO categories, those will be enforced by the schema and libpnd!-->
<categories>
<category name="Game">
<subcategory name="ActionGame"/>
</category>
</categories>
<clockspeed frequency="800"/>
</application>
</PXML>
